Whoo! I'm all sweaty.
Wanna log on to Second Life
and go swimming?
(Sheldon:)I just built a virtual pool.
(Leonard:)No. I can't look at you
or your avatar right now.
[PENNY LAUGHS]
Sounds like your neighbor's home.
(Leonard:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)Don't forget the mail you took
so you'd have an excuse to talk to her.
(Leonard:)Oh, right, right, right.
(Howard:)Stealing snail mail, very old school.
I like it.
(Leonard(exiting to hallway):)Penny, the mailman did it again. He...
Oh, sorry.
(Penny:)Um, no, hi, Leonard. This is Doug.
- Doug, this is my neighbor, Leonard.
- What's up, bro?
(Leonard:)Not much.
Bro. Heh.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, no. I just...
I got your mail again, here.
Oh, thank you.
I've got to talk to that mailman.
(Leonard:)Oh, no, that's probably
not such a good idea.